/**
 * Product Database can be added here.
 * You can add products of your wish with different attributes
 * */

export const quizzes = [
  {
    _id: "3fe39675-140b-4075-82f3-949a4dc95d18",
    title: "Sports",
    PointsPerQuestion: 5,
    totalScore: 25,
    mcqs: [
      {
        _id: 1,
        question: "What is the object hit by the players in ice hockey called?",
        options: ["Yawk", "Puck", "Gawk", "Ice Ball"],
        answer: "Puck",
      },
      {
        _id: 2,
        question: "From what country does Lego come?",
        options: ["Russia", "USA", "China", "Denmark"],
        answer: "Denmark",
      },
      {
        _id: 3,
        question: "How many holes are there on a standard golf course?",
        options: ["10", "18", "16", "12"],
        answer: "18",
      },
      {
        _id: 4,
        question: "In which sport might you do a slam dunk?",
        options: ["Baseball", "Basketball", "Volleyball", "Throwball"],
        answer: "Basketball",
      },
      {
        _id: 5,
        question: "Ping-pong is an alternative name for which sport?",
        options: ["Lawn Tennis", "Judo", "Table Tennis", "Badminton"],
        answer: "Table Tennis",
      },
    ],
    categoryName: "Sports",
  },
  {
    _id: "8eed23b3-b0f5-490c-bd72-66d0b0efe40f",
    title: "Technology",
    PointsPerQuestion: 5,
    totalScore: 25,
    mcqs: [
      {
        _id: 1,
        question: "Who founded Apple Computer?",
        options: ["Stephen Fry", "Bill Gates", "Steve Jobs", "Stephen Hawking"],
        answer: "Steve Jobs",
      },
      {
        _id: 2,
        question: "What does the Internet prefix WWW stand for?",
        options: [
          "Wide Width Wickets",
          "World Wide Web",
          "Worldwide Weathe",
          "Western Washington World",
        ],
        answer: "World Wide Web",
      },
      {
        _id: 3,
        question: "Who invented flexible photographic film?",
        options: [
          "Leonardo da Vinci",
          "Linda Eastman",
          "Louis Daguerre",
          "George Eastman",
        ],
        answer: "George Eastman",
      },
      {
        _id: 4,
        question: "Which of these is a file format for digital images?",
        options: ["CIA", "PDF", "JPG", "IBM"],
        answer: "JPG",
      },
      {
        _id: 5,
        question: "OS computer abbreviation usually means?",
        options: [
          "Order of Significance",
          "Open Software",
          "Operating System",
          "Operating System",
        ],
        answer: "Table Tennis",
      },
    ],
    categoryName: "Technology",
  },
  {
    _id: "276a88a4-9b86-4284-8e6e-8048b7e06b80",
    title: "Animals",
    PointsPerQuestion: 5,
    totalScore: 25,
    mcqs: [
      {
        _id: 1,
        question: "What animal is pregnant for the shortest time?",
        options: ["Shark", "Dolphin", "Whale", "Opossum"],
        answer: "Opossum",
      },
      {
        _id: 2,
        question: "Which is the largest dog in the world?",
        options: ["Shepard", "Retriever", "Bulldog", "Mastiff"],
        answer: "Mastiff",
      },
      {
        _id: 3,
        question: "What is the heaviest and tallest Penguin?",
        options: [
          "Emperor Penguin",
          "King Penguin",
          "Prince Penguin",
          "Servant Penguin",
        ],
        answer: "Emperor Penguin",
      },
      {
        _id: 4,
        question: "What percentage of DNA a chimpanzee shares with human?",
        options: ["75%", "98%", "12%", "0%"],
        answer: "98%",
      },
      {
        _id: 5,
        question: "What is Columbidae?",
        options: ["Bird", "Insect", "Reptile", "Lizard"],
        answer: "Bird",
      },
    ],
    categoryName: "Animals",
  },
];
